<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

   <statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
     <statement id="1">A few heavy smoke days from prescribed fires are better than constant, less smoky days over several months.</statement>
     <statement id="2">Dealing with frequent, mild smoke from prescribed fires is better than facing the dangers of heavy wildfire smoke.</statement>
     <statement id="3">Even a little smoke makes it hard to breathe.</statement>
     <statement id="4">I’m fine with a bit of smoke from prescribed fires here and there if it means my family and home are safer.</statement>
     <statement id="5">Fewer days with more smoke are better than a lot of days with less smoke.</statement>
     <statement id="6">I don’t care about how often prescribed burns are burned because I don’t want a big wildfire nearby.</statement>
     <statement id="7">Any prescribed fire is good, so I don’t care how often they burn or how much smoke they produce.</statement>
     <statement id="8">I’m fine with either high or low frequency smoke, just don’t burn near schools or hospitals.</statement>
     <statement id="9">More frequent prescribed burns are worth it if they mean avoiding catastrophic wildfires.</statement>
     <statement id="10">The thickness of smoke is more important than how often smoke happens.</statement>
     <statement id="11">There’s no such thing as ‘safe smoke,’ no matter how often or how intense.</statement>
     <statement id="12">I trust prescribed fire managers from state agencies to manage prescribed fires responsibly.</statement>
     <statement id="13">Prescribed fire managers prioritize meeting acreage targets over protecting the public from smoke.</statement>
     <statement id="14">The state government often fails to listen when prescribed fire smoke impacts rural communities.</statement>
     <statement id="15">State agencies are doing the best they can to manage prescribed fires under tough conditions.</statement>
     <statement id="16">Prescribed fires rarely turn into wildfires.</statement>
     <statement id="17">There needs to be more transparency from state agencies about when and why they use prescribed fires.</statement>
     <statement id="18">State agencies act in the public’s interest, even if they make mistakes.</statement>
     <statement id="19">The public should have more say in when and where state agencies use prescribed fires.</statement>
     <statement id="20">It’s hard to trust state agencies when prescribed fires seem to happen with no warning.</statement>
     <statement id="21">Private landowners who use prescribed fires on their own land are more careful than state agencies.</statement>
     <statement id="22">Prescribed burn associations are just as trustworthy as state agencies to manage prescribed fires responsibly.</statement>
     <statement id="23">I don't trust private landowners to consider how their prescribed fires affect my health.</statement>
     <statement id="24">Prescribed burn associations are more transparent about their burns than state agencies in my area.</statement>
     <statement id="25">Prescribed fire managers and people like me want the same thing: healthy forests and safe communities.</statement>
     <statement id="26">Prescribed fire managers don’t understand what matters most to local residents.</statement>
     <statement id="27">Prescribed fire managers need to consider how smoke affects families and vulnerable groups.</statement>
     <statement id="28">There’s a disconnect between public values and the priorities of prescribed fire managers.</statement>
     <statement id="29">I support prescribed burning because it helps maintain healthy wildlife habitat.</statement>
     <statement id="30">Prescribed fire managers care about wildlife just as much as I do.</statement>
     <statement id="31">I have heard that fires are good for wildlife, but I’ve seen animals flee from smoke and flames.</statement>
     <statement id="32">Prescribed fires on public lands should prioritize protecting wildlife, not just reducing wildfire risk.</statement>
     <statement id="33">Prescribed fires bring back birds, deer, and other species I care about.</statement>
     <statement id="34">Keeping people healthy should be the top priority, even if it means prescribed burning less often.</statement>
     <statement id="35">Some smoke from prescribed fires may be worth it if it prevents even worse health impacts from wildfires.</statement>
     <statement id="36">Prescribed fires help reduce risks for firefighters during wildfire season.</statement>
     <statement id="37">Protecting wildland firefighter lives is just as important as protecting forests.</statement>
     <statement id="38">I’ve seen prescribed fires protect my community from wildfires.</statement>
     <statement id="39">Wildfire smoke made me sick, and I now support anything that reduces the risk of smoke exposure from any kind of fire.</statement>
     <statement id="40">I’ve had positive experiences with prescribed fires increasing flowering plants.</statement>
     <statement id="41">A wildfire came too close to my home, and now I see prescribed fires very differently.</statement>
     <statement id="42">I grew up around prescribed fires, it’s just part of life here.</statement>
     <statement id="43">I’ve never had a bad experience with any fire, and I don’t see what the big deal is.</statement>
     <statement id="44">My neighborhood still smells like smoke for days after a prescribed fire, and it’s frustrating.</statement>
     <statement id="45">A wildfire came too close to my property, and I now wish more prescribed fires had been done.</statement>
     <statement id="46">Prescribed fires make the land greener, healthier, and better for wildlife.</statement>
     <statement id="47">I respect the reasons for burning, even if I don’t like the smoke.</statement>
   </statements>